I'm Tim Gipson, and I'm going to talk to you about trouble shooting your refrigerator.
Now, if you don't have any power at all to your refrigerator, first few things you want to check is you want to check and make sure that the breaker is not tripped in your main breaker box.
So you want to locate where that is, and you want to check the breaker and make sure it is reset.
If it is popped, you want to make sure you reset it to the on position.
The next thing would be to check the power chord behind the refrigerator and make sure it hasn't come loose from the outlet.
So that's basically on the power.
Now, if you still are not, do not have power, you may need to consult a professional repair service at that point, because there could be something internal to the refrigerator.
Now this particular refrigerator, it has all electronic controls, so it has its own sensors, which really tell you what's going on.
This particular model, up here, if you have some food that may not be staying cool enough, you might check your temperature controls.
This particular model actually tells you what the degrees are set to.
Recommended settings are anywhere from about 34 degrees to 38 degrees, depending on really how cold you like to keep some of your products, particularly dairy products.
Then the other side here, on the freezer side, some of the common things you can run in to is whether your ice maker is not distributing ice properly, or your water's not coming out.
Now if water's not coming out, most of these are equipped with a filter, so in this case, this one tells you when it's time to start thinking about ordering a filter, and it tells you when to replace it.
On the ice, occasionally, you may just need to come in here, where these are frost free freezers, this can actually warm up, or some of your ice melts together, and the agitating arm can actually get stuck.
So you want to come in here and break up your ice occasionally.
So I'm Tim Gipson, and that's some trouble shooting tips for your refrigerator.